<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Explorer</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Explorer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>/blog/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/day-1/</guid>
      <description> Day 1 Start weight - 207.4
 9:30 AM - Green Tea
Green Tea
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Summer 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/new-england-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/new-england-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>Vermont &amp;amp; New Hampshire Trip Day 1 June 29  Landed at Newark Airport Ate Roti falafel for lunch Started driving toward New Haven Dinner at Frank Pepe Pizza Started driving towards Barnet, VT at around 8.00 pm Reached the rented house at 1.30 am. It was an adventure to locate the house late at night with no cell phone reception. The house was impressive, location was great and it felt that there was no other soul around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe Summer 2017</title>
      <link>/blog/europe-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/europe-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>Europe Summer 2017 Trip Countries visited Switzerland, Italy, Montenegro, Greece, Croatia Day 1  As hurricane harvey was approaching US the trip was in serious doubt. But luckily the planes left before the hurricane made landfall. We landed next day in Zurich Took the train from Zurich to Bern, then Bern to Interlaken, and then Interlaken to Grindelwald Reached Grindlewald hotel around 4 pm Had greasy pizza for dinner, then had a relaxing evening while a band played American country music  Grindelwald Hotel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand 2014</title>
      <link>/blog/new-zealand-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/new-zealand-2014/</guid>
      <description>New Zealand Fall 2014 Trip Countries visited New Zealand &amp;amp; Tahiti Day 1, Oct 27 2014  Left from LA on Oct 26th to Papeete and then from Papeete to Auckland (Air Tahiti Nui) Arrived in Auckland on the afternoon of Oct 27th, and checked into the Waldorf Stadium Apartment Hotel Since we were travelling with an infant we selected a hotel with kitchen The apartments had kitchen and other facilities to cook our own food Had pizza for Dinner and then walked around the city and went grocery shopping   Auckland Hotel</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>